

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Alex. I'm a web developer with over ten years of experience in the field. I am very driven and motivated, and I believe that each day should be challenging and rewarding.

+63926-695-8485

alexpolo01@gmail.com

San Jose del Monte, Bulacan, Philippines

SKILLS

Web Development

- 1.Codelgniter
- 2.jQuery
- 3. Bootstrap
- 4.PHP
- 5. MySQL
- 6.HTMI
- 7.CSS
- 8. Javascript
- 9. Python
- Android Development (Java)

EXPERIENCE

Information Technology Officer 2020 - Present Philippine Statistics Authority

Leads the team in development of in-house application to support operations of the organizations.

INFORMATION SYSTEMS ANALYST 2013 - 2020 Philippine Statistics Authority

Designs and develops applications for use of the organization. Conducts training on new technologies in Android development.

STATISTICIAN 2010 - 2013 National Statistics Authority

Processes and analyzes survey forms used for national economic indicators

EDUCATION

Polytechnic University of the Philippines Bachelor of Science in Mathematics 2005 - 2009

CERTIFICATIONS

What is Data Science?

Coursera - J8N5KJ6CAFCV

Introduction to DevOps

Coursera - L53VHHQL55XL

Fundamentals of Network Communication

Coursera - XZ9J9YFWV8ST

Al For Everyone

Coursera - FAMQH5MDCQPW

Cloud Computing Basics (Cloud 101)

Coursera - SQ9E5TRS9SWL